{
    "id": "6f65acc91f4e453aa12fda97d3282002",
    "title": "Gap Filling Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We went …………………………… in the morning.",
            "description": "There is no preposition in the expression go swimming, go walking, go climbing etc.",
            "answers": [
                "swimming",
                "for swimming",
                "to swimming"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c4583461ec4c48b594500dfeb5d1ff1c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s ……………………….. something.",
            "description": "Let is followed by an infinitive without to. ",
            "answers": [
                "to eat",
                "eat",
                "eating"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8ba52f08aad04d12a0806a6c8d39ef5e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I went …………………….. Canada to meet my brother.",
            "description": "Use to to show direction. ",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "942816df299d4a74858fe3d7fbc65e3b"
        },
        {
            "question": "She went dancing ……………………….. the room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "into"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2b8e6d6fe7724a5889f7c9e89357587d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have invited all of my friends ……………………. my party.",
            "description": "You are invited to a specific event.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "at",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bc11c692b59245a5ba6d9fd1f43313d7"
        },
        {
            "question": "You .................... get some rest.",
            "description": "Had better is used to give strong advice.  ",
            "answers": [
                "have better",
                "had better",
                "better"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "603a5845723e4222988af75921f44a9c"
        },
        {
            "question": "One of my cousins ……………………… a singer.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after one of.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d16a25f3902240bfa33ae8db77ebe994"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher had scarcely left the class ………………………. the children started talking.",
            "description": "Scarcely is followed by when or before.",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "then",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "17e86268f17e41a9bcaecec5d77eb274"
        },
        {
            "question": "No sooner had I opened the door, …………………….. the cat jumped out.",
            "description": "We use than after no sooner.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "then",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "eff3792b5d2d49349635ab8944ebf23a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was hardly inside the house ……………………… it started raining.",
            "description": "Hardly is followed by when or before.",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "before",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "84572ae84d0b4cf9a55af08114624f68"
        },
        {
            "question": "How about …………………….. a drink?",
            "description": "Use an ing form after how about and what about.",
            "answers": [
                "to have",
                "having"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ae94104552944bec9c4220c756b001f7"
        },
        {
            "question": "She accused me ...................... stealing her watch.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "of",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9bf1d4e68a7d4896b10388863cb06419"
        }
    ]
}